theopinion.in 2011-12-11

# Privacy Policy | The Opinion

December 11, 6879 1:23 pm

Any opinions that are expressed here are purely the author’s opinion.

  * **Email** **–** Email address mentioned in the comment form will always be use for privacy and never be used for spamming. Though we recommend you never post your Email into the comments, so that other can’t see it. Even if you do, make sure you follow this format admin[at]gmail.com.
  * **Comments** – We love comments, but any comments which is abusive, spread hatred, racial or any way hurting anyone opinion will never be entertained. We keep our comments moderated to maintain the integrity of individuals.
  * **Cookie/Tracking Technology** – We may use cookies and tracking technology which are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Third parties such as our advertisers may also use cookies to collect information in the course of serving ads to you. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. Google, in particular, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * **RSS and Email Subscriptions** – This website records information about how people access our RSS feeds, but does not collect any personally identifying information from or about our RSS subscribers. This website’s feed services collect the e-mail addresses of individuals that subscribe to our RSS feed via e-mail. Individual information about subscribers to this website’s feed is held in strict confidence; we will not release or disclose any specific subscriber information under any circumstances, unless required by law. Aggregated information stripped of any personally identifiable information may be disclosed.
  * **External Links** – The web site contains links to other websites not owned by the owner of this website. We will not, and cannot, control how your personal information is used on these other websites. Consult the privacy policies of the linked websites to see how they use your information
  * **Privacy Contact Information** – If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may [Contact Us](http://theopinion.in/contact-us/)

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
